<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BLOG on SXY</title>
    <link>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/categories/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BLOG on SXY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/&#34;&gt;SXY&lt;/a&gt; 2018~2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UNSTABLE NARRATIVES，ACT1</title>
      <link>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/posts/eighth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/posts/eighth/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really sorry that you need to move here:, I can&amp;rsquo;t upload any image in our unstable narratives blog site :(
In this week&amp;rsquo;s exploration, I mainly observed plants. I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in their &amp;ldquo;life&amp;rdquo;, daily life and life journey.
    I first continued to observe a plant I saw when I was passing by. It seemed very common, but I never noticed its change from day to night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNSTABLE NARRATIVES，ABOUT ME</title>
      <link>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/posts/sixth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/posts/sixth/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I’m Xiaoya Sun from China, Beijing, and I’m currently on the Experimental Communication pathway.
I think I am a real indoorsy girl.
  There are very few outdoor activities in my life. I browsed my photo album and found that the only thing related to the outdoors is the sky and clouds, and then I was thinking, how boring life I am living?
  Maybe because I always feel tired when I went out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHO AM I FOR THE UNIVERSE? Scroll book, 62 pages</title>
      <link>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/posts/forth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/posts/forth/</guid>
      <description>The Theory of Everything (2014)   A paradox—— We are so curious about ourselves so that we have infinite curiosity about the universe we live in. The sense of restlessness comes from the limitations of cognition, and the limitations are the most prominent features of our role in universe.
  Pale_Blue_Dot (Seen from about 6 billion kilometers   -Carl Sagan , American astronomer:
Our planet is nothing more a grain of &amp;ldquo;dust suspended in the air&amp;rdquo; (1994).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SETTING UP YOUR ROBOT，Questionnaire，20cm*230cm</title>
      <link>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/posts/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/posts/third/</guid>
      <description>The idea comes from &amp;ldquo;a quarrel&amp;rdquo;.
I asked my boyfriend if he would like to try to fall in love with the robot. He actually replied &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo; without thinking.
I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it, maybe because I am his girlfriend, but even more terrifying is that I feel that he is optimistic about the development of robots in the follow-up conversation. He firmly believes that one day, the robot can Have &amp;ldquo;personality&amp;rdquo; and learn the so-called “self-learning&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1984, Interactive Installation, in a 7m*7m space</title>
      <link>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/posts/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cuuuuuutie.github.io/posts/second/</guid>
      <description>It is a device that combines time and sound.
“Time”, “Surrender”, “Scream”, “Death”
  1984   I read this book several times. For a long time, when I was walking, taking the subway, sleeping, I was surrounded by the emotion and atmosphere in the book, I have been deep infected by Winston&amp;rsquo;s pursuit and struggle, his hope and despair. The resonance this book brings to me is not historical, but it is similar to many things in my life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
